[Owen. Seth grunting]
[Bailey] Stop it! Stop!
[Owen panting]
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I thought you were dead.
You know what I should do?
I should call Frank right now.
Frank? No. please. Look. it's her father.
- Please don't call. [breathing heavily]
- Grandpa.
- All right.
- [breathing heavily]
- [Owen] It's okay.
It's okay.
You're okay?
We're fine. Everyone…
Everyone's fine. [sighs]
How could you put Bailey
and Hannah at risk like that?
You put them at risk.
I told you not to go after Frank.
I told you as soon as you were gone.
they would come after them.
Well. they tried to kill me
because you messed with his business.
[Owen] The deal you and Hannah made
wasn't sustainable.
You can't make deals with these animals.
You of all people should know that.
- [Nicholas] Me of all people?
- Owen.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- What do you think it means?
How many more people do you have to lose
before you realize what you've done?
So fucking what?
[both speak indistinctly]
You start talking about my daughter.
you won't have to worry about Frank.
'cause I'm gonna go
after you my fucking self.
Enough! Enough! [panting]
Let's not start litigating the past.
At least not before
all of us are somewhere safe.
Charlie?
We should get out of the city.
We should head out to Lake Travis.
You want me to invite this asshole
into my house?
Hey.
This asshole
happens to be Bailey's father.
I'm sure she'd rather you not throw him
to the wolves.
Well. you're on borrowed time.
Believe me.
I don't plan to overstay my welcome.
[Hannah] Let's go. Charlie.
Seth. can you bring the cars around back?
We can sneak out through the alley.
Wait. It's safer if you ride without me.
- Wait. really?
- [Nicholas] He's right.
I'd rather he ride with us.
[stammers]
What exactly are you worried about?
Well. other than
you two killing each other?
It's fine. I'll be fine.
[Seth] We should move.
- Where's Dad?
- He's riding in the other car.
You think that's a good idea?
No. I don't.
Yeah. It's Sully.
Yeah. two SUVs just left.
[Teddy] Two SUVs?
Why the fuck does Charlie need two SUVs?
- Protection.
- [Sully] Do you want me to follow it?
- Do you want him to follow?
- No.
No. we're good.
What's Charlie got to be afraid of?
He thinks that Nicky's death
wasn't an accident.
Bullshit. He had a heart attack.
The coroner found traces
of poison in his blood.
Well. Nicky wasn't everybody's favorite.
He was mine.
- Where are we on Ethan Young?
- [Teddy] I'm on it.
[sighs] We think he's in Austin.
His wife and kid too.
We should talk.
About what?
We should talk about
how we're gonna protect them.
Did it ever strike you that every time
you try to protect them.
they wind up in more danger?
[Bailey] The two of them were so angry.
Yeah. Some old wounds there.
They see things so differently.
[chuckles] That's an understatement.
So who do you think is right?
Look. the Campanos broke the law
and so did my father.
But whether his work for the Campanos had
anything to do with your mother's death…
[stammers. sighs]
It's funny. I always believed
that Grandpa must have been wrong.
But seeing my dad today. that anger…
Well. it just made me wonder.
What if it was my dad who was wrong?
Those two men. it's… it's not surprising
they bring out the worst in each other.
I wouldn't read too much into it.
You know your father.
- Did we ever discuss chaos theory?
- What?
I studied fractals at UT.
we must have discussed chaos theory.
I honestly have no idea
what the hell you're talking about.
Chaotic systems seem random. but there
are connections. underlying patterns.
[stammers] A butterfly flaps its wings
in Austin.
- you get a tornado in Sausalito.
- Get to the fucking point.
It's why I did what I did.
I couldn't put the pieces together.
I-I didn't know exactly what lead to
Kate's death. but I knew it wasn't random.
I knew somehow
it had to do with that family.
No. You don't know
what the fuck you're talking about.
[scoffs] They just tried to kill you.
Isn't that what you said?
- That wasn't Frank.
- You don't know that.
You can't know that.
which is exactly my point.
Kate tried to warn me.
She…
She hated the fact
that you'd wrapped me up in it.
She…
She knew the second you crossed the line
and started helping Frank break the law.
Seth. Stop the car.
You don't get these people.
You never have.
If I made any mistake.
it was in trusting you.
For God's sake.
your daughter was the only thing that gave
me any solace at all after Kate's death.
- And you took her away from me.
- For her own good.
[scoffs] Bullshit.
- You were punishing me.
- What?
- That's all. It was rash. it was stupid.
- Jesus Christ.
It was the first in a long line
of terrible decisions
that upended the lives of everyone
you've come in contact with since.
No. You're wrong. Nicholas.
It wasn't about you.
It was always about her.
It was about keeping her safe.
You want to keep her safe? All right.
There. All right.
- [sighs]
- That's Frank's number.
- Call him.
- [stammers]
Turn yourself in.
And then Bailey and Hannah and I
can go on with our fucking lives.
[Hannah] Will you call him again. Charlie?
I just tried them.
The service around here is not great.
Yeah.
- He's not a monster. Hannah.
- Mm-hmm.
Is that…
Oh. thank God.
[breathes shakily]
I told Seth minimal staff.
The less people know he's here.
the better.
- Yep.
- Hey.
- How'd that go?
- Great.
[car door opens]
Do you want me to ride home with you?
I got a driver.
Also. I'm not a fucking infant.
Okay. I'll see you in the morning.
Yeah. it's me. Any trace of them?
Stay on it.
I need to put an end
to this Ethan Young bullshit.
Speaking of which. I got a thing
I need you to clean up for me.
[Owen] Grady's gone.
The case is gone.
And everything I've done has just put you
and Bailey in more danger.
The danger was already there.
- It was only a matter of time.
- Maybe. Or maybe I'm the problem.
I knew you shouldn't
have been in that car with Nicholas.
Convince me it's not the best thing
for all of us.
- For you to sacrifice yourself?
- [stammers] I could disappear again.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- [stammers]
After all that Bailey has been through.
you want to abandon her again?
- I don't want to… I'm trying to--
- Okay. stop it.
Stop it. You can't leave us again.
Not now.
Get it out of your head.
Okay.
[Nicholas]
I want to be clear about something.
I am not a fan
of this playing with jokers.
It speeds up the game.
My point exactly.
I thought Gin was a way
to enjoy passing the time.
You also used to think that driving was a
good way to get from Austin to Sausalito.
Just because I don't like planes.
I'm just saying that some things
are better when they go faster.
Well. you're gonna regret
saying that when I win.
[chuckles]
Hmm.
I know you and my dad used to be close.
That was a long time ago.
Charlie said you treated him like a son.
That was before your mother…
You know what he did.
He was reckless and wrong about a lot.
What about you?
There's nothing you were wrong about?
Plenty. But not this.
I made choices.
And there were consequences.
But I am not about to second-guess myself
because of some damn fool's
baseless theories.
Maybe you should start.
Gin.
What about your case against the Campanos?
- Can we build it up again?
- Most of the evidence is gone.
there's no easy way to get it back.
Okay. but if we could--
Well. we'd still have to prove that Teddy
and Frank knew about the shipments
for it to hold up in a court of law.
What if we were operating
outside the legal system?
We don't need to take down
the Campano's organization.
we just need to convince them
to leave us alone.
Okay. But how?
At the Never Dry. when I suggested that
maybe Teddy had poisoned Nicholas.
Frank went nuts.
You think…
You think Frank's losing control.
If Teddy poisoned Nicholas
without Frank's knowledge…
Then maybe Teddy's been doing business
with the Syndicate
without Frank's knowledge.
We prove that Teddy's been going rogue.
we might be able to convince Frank
he's got a bigger problem than us.
Here.
- That's Teddy.
- [Hannah] Mm-hmm.
- Bingo can. but that's long gone.
- Right.
I have to find another can
and tie it to Teddy.
I thought we'd moved
from "I" to "we." [chuckles]
Yeah.
but this involves going to Houston.
breaking into the shipyard.
It's gonna be dangerous.
Then it's good
you'll have me there to help.
[Ed] I understand. Okay.
[Maris] You're here late.
Uh. yes. just finishing up some paperwork.
Is that right?
- I just… [sighs]
- Can't let it go. huh?
[sighs] Not really.
Well. then you'll like this.
Delia called me.
Confidentially. forensics found a print
on Grady's storage locker.
- Is the FBI into it?
- They are.
but I figured it wouldn't hurt
to do a little digging on our own.
- Yeah. Yeah. yeah. of course.
- Since you and Grady were close.
[Maris] Ed? You okay?
Yeah. [stutters] I'll do some follow-up.
- Great. Don't stay too late.
- Uh-huh.
[Hannah panting]
Thanks for the sweats.
Of course. Good run?
Oh. it was great. It's beautiful out.
They ran your obituary.
[Nicholas] Mm-hmm.
And you see how small the photo is?
- [sighs] I thought I owned this town.
- Oh. how quickly they move on.
Yeah.
Maybe you should try it.
You know how hard this is for me?
I have an idea.
I also happen to know how you feel
about your granddaughter.
I'm guessing you love her
more than you hate him.
All right. Anything else. counselor?
Yes. actually.
You're going to Houston
to break into the shipyard?
I know the place.
It's not as bad as it sounds.
It sounds pretty bad.
Bails. I'm trying to find a way--
What? Nicholas said I was safe. so this…
this isn't about protecting me.
I don't exactly trust Nicholas.
but even if I did.
I'd still wanna find a way
for all of us to be together.
That's gonna be pretty hard
if the Campano's catch you.
- Bails--
- Did you even talk to Hannah about this?
It was kind of her idea.
Hey.
- Nicholas is on board.
- He is?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you like this plan?
You think he should go to Houston?
Not on his own.
[sighs] So you're both crazy.
Great. [scoffs]
Bailey.
I won't go if you don't want me to.
But I think I can be helpful.
We can't just keep running.
We need to do something.
[sighs]
We'll come back in one piece. I promise.
You better.
Yeah.
You stay safe
and keep your grandfather out of trouble.
[scoffs] Like I have any control over him.
Well. you have more
than you think. [chuckles]
["A Matter of Minutes" playing]
♪ I've been thinking
About you and me ♪
This is nice.
Driving through the Texas heartland
to stop a crime family from killing us?
Well. I think they just want me.
But. yeah.
[sighs]
Bailey and I… we. um…
We met Quinn Campano.
Bailey reached out to her.
She thought Quinn might be able
to tell her something about her mother.
- Okay.
- Apparently they were close?
Quinn and Kate?
They were all close.
Quinn. Kate. Charlie. Teddy.
I never liked Teddy.
but Quinn. she was a good egg.
What about Kate?
I want to know.
[mutters]
I'm sure Charlie and Nicholas
told you about her.
You see. an evasive answer to an intimate
question is not the way to a girl's heart.
She was smart.
Really smart.
Tough. If you grew up around Nicholas.
you better be.
Yeah.
She'd see right through you.
cut you down to size.
Which was a lot. even if she wasn't so…
So beautiful?
It's fine. I wanna know.
I wanna… I wanna know about you.
I was… I was a poor kid from nowhere.
she was Austin royalty.
I mean. they knew everyone on campus.
in town.
And… And she…
she was very much at the center of it all.
I was in love with her and her world.
It was like nothing I'd ever experienced.
I never stood a chance.
See. that's some good first date material.
Is that what this is?
I don't know.
She sounds like she was amazing.
She was the most amazing woman
I'd ever met until I met you.
- [music resumes]
- ♪ Nothing was saved in time ♪
♪ And all of my old world
And all the things in it ♪
♪ Are hard to find ♪
[music ends]
[Jimmy] So I've graduated
from the late night booty call. huh?
[chuckles]
Or maybe not?
I… It's just we're near my office. so…
- Oh. got it.
- [chuckles]
Don't want anyone knowing
you're dating a bad boy. right?
[chuckles] I wouldn't call it dating.
What's going on?
[Ed] Uh… Nothing. um…
That-That marshal who died?
We got a lead in his case.
Um… I thought the guy OD'd? [scoffs]
We don't think so. He had
a storage locker someone cleared out.
Makes us think something else is going on.
Huh. Wow.
Um… And you have a specific lead?
No. but. um…
we found a print at the storage locker
we're running through the FBI's system.
Why?
No reason. I just. um…
Well. I could see how that'd be.
you know. upsetting.
Yeah.
Oh. shit. I just realized
I've got a work thing.
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah. I'm…
I'm so sorry. Uh. rain check?
Uh-huh.
[Owen] This is it.
[Hannah] Do you know how to find
the container we're looking for?
[Owen] Yeah. I've memorized the yard map.
[sighs. stammers]
They've got cameras everywhere.
Can we avoid 'em?
[sighs] It's dicey.
Is this where you tell me
it'd be better if I stayed put?
Well…
wouldn't be much of a date if you did.
[sighs]
What do we do about the cameras?
We wait until night falls.
And then we proceed very carefully.
[Nicholas] Whatcha got there?
Uh. Charlie gave me
some of Mom's old things.
[sighs] These photos.
He said she liked to take them.
I'm sorry that I…
I shut you down last night.
I know it's a sore subject.
I just want to understand.
You know. I. uh…
I started as a. uh.
legal aid lawyer out of UT?
Hmm.
Yeah. I helped people
who couldn't afford to help themselves.
It's what I wanted to do.
So. how did you wind up with Frank?
I represented a kid who worked for him.
I did well and he. uh…
Frank. he offered me a lot of money.
We were just starting a family. so…
Did you know what he did?
[Nicholas] Yeah. I had a rough idea.
Look. everyone deserves a fair trial.
There is nothing wrong
with defending someone like Frank.
But there are lines that you don't cross.
[Bailey] And you crossed them?
[sighs]
Yeah.
Yeah. ten years in. the feds…
they got Frank on a bullshit felony.
And we knocked it down to six months.
but that is a long time behind bars…
when you're running an organization.
Frank. he asked me to. uh.
pass messages for his guys.
- And that's…
- That is the line.
And I should've pushed back harder.
but we were close.
And Frank. he was persuasive.
[sighs]
You asked my dad for help with that.
Right?
Yeah. Later. I told him if he wasn't
comfortable. he didn't have to do it.
But he looked up to you.
He wasn't doing anything wrong. and
everything would've been fine if. uh--
If my mom hadn't died? [scoffs]
He could've just kept on
helping you break the law?
[sighs]
[chuckles] I think we've got
another lawyer in the family.
- She's gonna be after your job. Nicky.
- More for the banana monster.
- [chuckles]
- I want those.
- What? Really?
- Oh.
- Oh. Look at that.
- [Kate laughs]
[video stops]
[line ringing]
[phone buzzes]
Okay. slow down.
- What exactly did she say?
- She said they'd found a print.
You weren't wearing gloves?
Yeah. but there was so much shit in there.
I tore up a couple pairs.
I mean.
I-I thought I was being careful. but…
[sighs] Jimmy.
[scoffs] She didn't mention the other job.
did she?
What? Nicky Bell? No.
No. they got nothing on that one.
[Teddy] You like Cabo?
[Jimmy] Who doesn't like Cabo?
Book a flight. spend a few weeks.
I'll let you know when the coast is clear.
- I appreciate that. Teddy.
- We take care of our people.
[shutter clicking]
So I thought about bringing
wine and cheese. but…
Screw the wine.
Mmm…
So… I understand you're a single mother?
That's good date material. right?
- I suppose.
- [chuckles]
Seriously. It's kind of amazing to watch.
You with Bailey.
Oh. she's a miracle.
Mmm. I recall her being something
less than miraculous with you.
Of course. I always knew eventually
she'd realize how great you are.
Don't do that.
- Don't do what?
- Don't make it sound like it's been easy.
It has not been easy.
- I didn't mean to suggest that--
- Do you have any idea how hard it was?
To do this alone?
I think I have some idea.
Okay.
Then what would you have done
the night she didn't come home
after Bobby's senior prom?
I mean. I-I was pretty sure she was
with him. but she hadn't called or texted.
and it's. like. 2:00 in the morning.
I was flipping out.
- Jules isn't picking up--
- I get it.
Okay. what about the night she called
stoned out of her mind
convinced the joint her sorority sister
gave her was laced with LSD?
- What would you have done?
- [stammers]
Or the time she showed up at the shop with
a false positive on the pregnancy test?
- Okay. Jesus. [sighs]
- Yeah. Exactly.
[stammers] I'm not sure how helpful
I would have been with any of that.
Oh. no. you would have definitely
made it worse.
But it would have been nice
to have you there.
For what it's worth. I wanted to be there.
And I want to be there now.
It's getting darker. We should go.
[car alarm chirps]
This way.
[Hannah] There are hundreds of containers.
This is Rafina's section.
The Campano's shipping company.
- This'll help us find it.
- [scanner beeping]
Okay.
[Hannah] So. wait. this is
one of the bingo cans?
[Owen] Yeah.
Wait. Wait.
Okay. This is it.
Okay.
[Owen grunts]
[Hannah] Toasters?
[Owen] Something's wrong.
Maybe it's just for show?
[Owen] No…
[Hannah] Do you think the scanner
picked up the wrong number?
[Owen] The number's on the door.
Could they have already removed the drugs?
The cans are sealed
until they reach their destination.
They must've changed the system
when they realized I was onto them.
- Okay. so… So how do we…
- I don't know.
I don't know if I don't know.
It took me months to figure out the code.
[Maris] We're just looking for
a level 2 injunction. Thanks. counselor.
Agent Buckley.
[sighs] Um… [breathes shakily]
I… [sighs] I made a mistake.
[sighs] Okay.
I think I might've gotten Grady killed.
[Hannah sighs]
[grunts]
[sighs]
We can't catch a fucking break.
Hey. can I see your camera?
Sure. Why?
Can you show me the picture
of Teddy with the containers?
[Hannah] Okay. look. Is that a bingo can?
- [Owen] Definitely. Yeah.
- That's the bingo can?
Owen. we don't need to find a new can.
We just need to find this one.
[stammers]
Well. this would've shipped already.
Okay. we just figure out
where it's headed.
We'd have to break into
the shipyard office. access the database…
[stammers] You saw the security…
Isn't there someone you used to work with
who has access to the database?
Wallace. the foreman of the west side
of the shipyard.
But… But he's a tool.
[stammers] For all I know. he's on
the Campanos' payroll. No way he'd help.
Well. no way he'd help you.
You don't even know the guy.
There's always a way
to get people talking.
[Charlie] Hey.
I found some more of these. I stashed 'em
in a couple different places.
[chuckles] I figured that was the best way
to keep them from getting thrown out.
Thanks. I'm glad you did.
What did you say to him?
Nothing. I… [sighs]
I just wanted to know about what happened.
Between him and your dad?
You're a brave lady.
Or a stupid one. Didn't go all that well.
Huh. I don't know.
He's thinking about it. whatever you said.
Which is pretty unusual.
- [Owen speaks indistinctly]
- [Kate] So fucking what?
- So fucking what?
- [Kate] Yes. fucking what.
[Quinn] Kristin.
Kristin.
[typing]
[line ringing]
[receptionist] Quinn Favreau's Office.
Hi. this is. uh. her friend Bailey.
Could I talk to her?
I'm sorry. Quinn isn't here.
She's working out of the Austin office.
She has an Austin office?
Yeah. I'm not sure you'll catch her.
but I can give you the number.
- [people chattering]
- [motorcycle revving]
So the Yard manifesto on the computer
in Wallace's office
should tell me where the can is heading?
Yeah. but how are you gonna get
Wallace back to his office?
I don't know.
Gonna have to figure that out.
It's a bad idea.
Have a little faith.
[scoffs]
[people chattering]
I'm gonna give you a lot of shit
for tomorrow. You know?
[laughs] All right. Take care.
Hi. Are you Wallace Kovacs?
Who's asking?
Sandra Lee Cooper.
I'm a journalist for The Atlantic.
- Oh. you're a journalist?
- Yeah.
Ah. No comment. [chuckles]
You don't know
what I wanna talk to you about yet.
Yeah. I don't… I don't need to know.
I'm sorry. I don't have any respect
for somebody who makes a living
typing out half-baked thoughts online
and ruining people's lives
in exchange for clicks. so piss off.
- Okay. I'll tell Timmy…
- Thank you.
…you didn't wanna talk. No problem.
Timmy?
Timmy Franz. You know him. right?
I mean. everybody knows Timmy.
I'm writing an article about AI and
the resilience of the blue-collar worker.
And Timmy said I had to talk to you
because you're the reason
this shipyard's turnaround rates
are world class.
Timmy said all that?
No. he did. Um…
I mean. if Timmy sent you and. uh.
you-you wouldn't mind
getting me another bottle of beer…
- Really?
- Yeah.
[Quinn] So you're in Austin.
Uh. yeah. there was a memorial
for my grandfather.
Right. My father went to that.
I gave him your message.
Thanks.
Uh. that's not why I'm here.
I had another question about my mom.
Okay.
[sighs] I… I keep having this memory. I'm…
[sighs] I'm. like. four years old
and I'm watching my parents fight
at a motel.
And it's not just bickering. It's…
It's. like. angry. aggressive.
And I must not have liked it because I…
I jumped into the pool
and I stayed there. underwater.
until…
Until?
Until you pulled me out.
Well. I don't remember that exactly.
But you remember something?
You and your mom went to a motel.
Just before she died.
Why? Why were we at a motel?
[inhales deeply] Your mom and dad
had a huge blowup.
and she took you there.
She said she needed some space.
She had to figure some things out.
What were they fighting about?
I don't know. but it was bad.
She didn't think they would recover.
Anyway. I came to visit.
I don't remember you in the pool.
but. uh… [sighs]
She didn't tell you
what they were fighting about?
[Quinn] She didn't want to.
She probably would've eventually.
but that day at the motel was the last
time I saw her before she died.
[inhales sharply] You're over 21. right?
I think we should have a drink.
- Yeah. baby.
- [people chattering]
[exclaims] I love that burn. I love it.
[groans] It's pretty good.
- [Wallace] Love it. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
You said Houston's port
is one of the world's largest. right?
Damn right it is.
Well. how do you keep track
of all the shipments?
I mean. is there a…
a database for all the ISO codes?
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
How do you know what an ISO code is?
Oh. um. my dad was pretty high up
at the Bureau of International Containers.
- He worked for the BIC?
- Yeah.
Oh. my God! Wow.
I used to love going to the office
with him.
I bet.
Your office must be pretty impressive too.
I mean. it's… it's not the BIC.
but we definitely do
try to keep up to their standards.
Wow.
I mean. I could… I could take you there
and show you if you like.
[gasps] You're so sweet.
- Okay.
- [chuckles]
[Quinn] I'm sorry.
I know this must be a lot for you.
A lot of secrets in my family.
Join the club.
Is there something else on your mind?
Charlie told me that my dad
did what he did
because he was convinced your family
had something to do with my mom's death.
You're asking me
if my family killed your mother.
[sighs] I… [sighs] I'm sorry.
- I… I didn't--
- Don't worry. I've heard a lot worse.
Why do you think I distance myself
from my father and my brother? [chuckles]
Bailey. I don't know
what happened to your mom.
But I learned a long time ago that knowing
the truth doesn't always provide comfort.
And getting there can take you
to a lot of really awful places.
So before you go any further. you need
to ask yourself how far you wanna go.
Especially because
it won't really change things.
Come on.
[sighs]
- It's all there in the database.
- Wow.
Yeah. any-any can in the world.
I just type in the container number
and the ISO code.
and bam!
I know where it is and where it's going.
- Wow.
- [chuckles]
- So cool.
- Isn't it?
[inhales sharply] Do you have any water?
- I'm feeling those shots. [chuckles]
- Yeah. sure.
- Ooh. me too. [laughs]
- Mmm.
Would you like plain water or bubbles?
Bubbles.
Okay. bubbles.
- Just gonna have a seat.
- Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Got some flavors here.
We got. uh… Let's see.
We got peach. plum and Pamplemousse.
- Pamplemousse.
- [chuckles] Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Pamplemousse it is.
[speaks indistinctly]
- Oh. Pamplemousse. Pamplemousse.
- Do you have any ice?
Ice. Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Pamplemousse and ice.
So. uh. what newspaper
did you say you work for again?
I'd like to show my buddies
where the article is.
- What?
- It's going to Marseille.
And Teddy's meeting it there.
Good job.
[knocks on door]
Hey. baby. Glad you called.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Where are you going?
- Uh. business trip.
- [door closes]
Gonna keep me away for a couple weeks.
but I don't fly out until the morning.
- so…
- [chuckles]
[chuckles] What's up?
Isn't this why you came?
[chuckles]
Why'd you get all weird on me earlier?
Just got shit going on. babe.
Shit that has to do
with the murder of a US Marshal?
The fuck?
You've been using me this whole time.
haven't you?
The Campanos needed eyes
on the marshal's office
and you've been playing me.
[gasps]
You're wearing a fucking wire?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Drop the gun! Drop it!
[gasps. breathes heavily]
[high-pitched ringing]
Ed? You good?
Yeah.
[sighs] Jimmy Esposito
was gunned down last night.
He was in your crew. right?
Any loose ends here?
None that'd tie him to us.
but our friend in the marshal's service
told me they found a small canister
of strychnine in his apartment.
Strychnine. That's the same poison
that was used on Nicholas.
God.
I'm sorry. Pop. It's my fault.
Jimmy liked to play hero.
I guess when he heard me
bitching about Owen.
how Nicky was the only thing
standing in our way…
I know how important Nicky was to you.
[sighs]
I'm sorry it went down like this.
You gotta keep your house in order. Teddy.
No matter how big it is.
a single crack in the foundation.
it's all fucked.
Yeah. I know. Pop.
I really am sorry.
And if it's any consolation.
the guy's dead. He got what he deserved.
Hey. I wanna go through the books.
Garages. shipping. everything.
No. I don't wanna bother Teddy.
Send it directly to me.
I keep thinking about you
at the Thirsty Barnacle.
Well. any excuse to get out of my RV.
Yeah. I can't believe you lived like that
for a year.
It was a way back to you.
[Nicholas] You're back.
You want to go to Marseille?
If this is Teddy.
and everything suggests that it is.
it's our best shot at proving to Frank
that Teddy's been going rogue.
- Hmm.
- [Hannah] Nicholas. what?
A year ago.
Frank was thinking of transitioning out.
giving Teddy full control.
He asked me what I thought.
I told him I thought it was a bad idea.
The next thing I knew. Teddy… he's here.
yelling into my security cameras.
completely manic.
- Did you tell Frank?
- [scoffs] No.
Teddy… he's always had a temper.
No. I was trying to keep the peace.
But maybe I should've.
Maybe this all could have been avoided.
[Owen] I don't think so.
When I worked at the port. Wallace told me
Teddy has been in charge of shipping
for the last 18 months.
That's how long he's been trying to get
into business with the Syndicate.
So you need to go to Marseille.
We need to get to the shipments
before Teddy can.
"We"?
Someone's gotta keep an eye on him.
[inhales deeply]
All right. Well. you fly commercial.
It's harder to track than private.
You sit in different rows.
take separate cars to the airport.
And Seth. he'll arrange the logistics.
Thank you.
Least I can do.
[Maris] I wanna be clear.
no one's blaming you here.
but there are several ongoing
investigations into the Campanos.
You know Delia.
from the US Attorney's office.
- Hi.
- [Ed] Hi.
This is my boss. Ivan Escarra. He's head
of the Organized Crime Task Force.
Hello. Mr. Escarra.
Ed. Ivan is fine.
Now. Ed. I-I know this is difficult.
but is there anything that Mr. Esposito
might have said about the Campanos that…
I-I already told Maris I… I didn't know
Jimmy was working with them until. um…
Of course. Um… [clears throat]
- Why don't we start from the beginning?
- Take it easy on her. hmm?
[Larry] She okay?
She will be. What's the paper?
So Ed said we got tipped off about Jimmy
from a fingerprint
at Grady's storage locker.
but… [stammers] …I mean. I can't seem
to find it in the evidence log.
[sighs] It's been a traumatic few days.
Maybe she's confused.
We did get a call into the tip line.
That must have been it.
Give her some room.
It's gonna take her a minute.
[Larry] You bet.
That's the number for our new burner
in case you need to get ahold of us.
Thought we were supposed
to make these decisions together.
We are.
- Hey. if you don't want us to go…
- No. don't… Don't do that. Don't pretend.
Bailey. [sighs]
We're close to a solution here.
You're starting to sound like him.
That's mean.
Well. if the crazy scheme fits…
[sighs] You really think this is crazy?
It's not not crazy.
My dad has made so many bad decisions.
I'm not sure we even know
the half of them.
I… I don't get
why you're following his lead here.
I'm not following his lead.
Okay. [scoffs]
I love you. Bailey.
Is she all right?
[Hannah] I think she's just
working through some things.
Can I ask you something?
If you knew then everything you know now…
would you do it all over again?
Don't ask that.
Not right now.
Ms. Hall. Might be traffic.
We should go.
I'll see you in Marseille.
Yeah.
["I Follow Rivers" playing]
♪ Oh. I beg you ♪
♪ Can I follow? ♪
♪ Oh. I ask you ♪
♪ Why not always ♪
♪ Be the ocean ♪
♪ Where I unravel? ♪
♪ Be my only ♪
♪ Be the water where I'm wading ♪
♪ You're my river running high ♪
♪ Run deep. run wild ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ I follow you
Deep sea baby ♪
♪ I follow you ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ He's a message ♪
♪ He's the rebel ♪
♪ I'm the daughter waiting for you ♪
[thunder rumbling]
♪ Run deep. run wild ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ I follow you
Deep sea baby ♪
♪ I follow you ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ I follow you
Dark room honey ♪
[thunder rumbling]
[music ends]